fiversworld.com 2014-12-17

# Privacy Policy - FiversWorld.com

**FiversWorld.com**  is providing this Privacy Policy to explain our dedication in protecting and respecting your privacy.  This provides information on how we collect, keep and release information we collect from the users of our website. By visiting FiversWorld.com as a user, you will abide to all the terms and conditions of our privacy policy. These terms can be updated on a regular basis and notification of important changes (update) posted on FiversWorld.com site.

**1\. Information We Collect**  
You may browse the FiversWorld.com® site without providing any personal information that may be used to identify you personally ('Personally Identifiable Information' or 'PII'). If you choose to provide us with your PII, you are agreeing to the processing and storage of your information in the United States and countries outside of the United States which may have data protection laws that differ from laws in your country.

(i) FiversWorld.com® explicitly asks when it needs PII. To help facilitate the question and response process, and the payment of Service providers via PayPal™, FiversWorld.com requires basic data such as email address. To obtain payments from customers, FiversWorld.com asks for either credit card information or PayPal™ email address, at the customer's election. Service Provider applicants and/or other participants may be asked for additional information, such as full names, email addresses, telephone numbers, and other information but not limited to. Buyers who win gigs on the site may be required to provide shipment addresses. If you choose to recommend potential Service providers to your friends, to tell a friend or others about FiversWorld.com, or send a copy of a gigs sequence to a friend, you may need to provide their email addresses (and possibly their and your names). If you choose to have FiversWorld.com notify you of responses to your questions via text message, you will be asked for your cellular phone number and Cellular Phone Company.  Other PII may be requested in certain circumstances or collected on a voluntary basis such as on users' profile or signature pages.

(ii) As explained in the FiversWorld.com® Terms of Service,  _information provided by you in the content of your gigs_ , services, and other posts on the Site, in service provider profiles describing your talents and skills, and in signatures attached to postings on the Site ('Posts')  _is not private or confidential_. This is an Internet-based forum and information submitted in Posts may be read, collected, and used by others, and FiversWorld.com is not responsible for it.  For example, search engines may index your questions, answers, and other Posts to allow them to  _appear in search engine results_  ( _e.g._  if someone does a search on google.com, your gigs, and other Posts on FiversWorld.com that relate to the search may appear in the google.com search results list). Protect your anonymity by not including your real name or any personally identifying information in your gigs, and other Posts on the Site.

(iii) In some cases, FiversWorld.com® supplements portions of the PII you provide with other data received from third parties, or data sent to us from your web browser including (depending on its settings) your IP address, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data ('Usage Statistics').

(iv)  To enhance and individualize your experience with FiversWorld.com®, we use a web browser feature called a 'cookie.' Cookies are small files that your browser places on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to let us know that you are a prior user and, if you wish, retrieve your username and password so you do not need to enter them again. Cookies are not used to store other personal information. FiversWorld.com® also uses cookies to maintain state. That is, each time you logon, our system issues your browser a unique, randomly generated number by which it can identify itself. In that way, your data gets sent to you and not someone else. You must activate cookies to logon to FiversWorld.com®. FiversWorld.com®also uses web beacons that collect non-PII to track site usage.

(v.) FiversWorld.com® is intended for adult use only. In addition, it does not knowingly solicit or collect PII from persons under 13 years old. We may delete from the site PII, as well as Posts and other information, from users we believe are under the age of 18.

**(2).Use of Your Information**  
FiversWorld.com® may use, share, transfer, or disclose your PII and/or Usage Statistics, itself or in conjunction with third parties, for payment processing, fraud prevention, customer service, demographic studies, to tailor FiversWorld.com®'s content and services to its users' needs, and to serve advertisements. To display advertisements that may interest you, FiversWorld.com® may/uses third-party advertising companies who may use Usage Statistics (not your name, address, email address or telephone number). To learn more about this third-party advertising practice and your choice to opt-out of having information about you used by these companies.

 (i) FiversWorld.com® currently has no parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control. If it does in the future, or if it merges with or sells its assets or its company to another, then it may share your PII with such companies, in which event it will require that such companies follow this Policy with respect to your PII, unless you are provided with prior written notice.

**(3.) Correspondence Sent to You**  
FiversWorld.com® will not send you any unsolicited information, including e-mail, except:  
(i) Users will receive FiversWorld.com® registration emails when they register, users will receive FiversWorld.com® communications relating to their applications, Service providers may receive daily digests of gigs asked in the categories in which they are service providers, and all users will receive updates and notices about gigs they are asking or needing, other Posts, their accounts, and new features and policies; these communications are considered part and parcel of your service and, except for the daily digests, you cannot opt out of them;

(ii) Periodically, FiversWorld.com® may contact you about new services, special offers, promotions and third-party / affiliate offers, and will include in any such emails an opt-out link by which you can opt out of receiving such emails; and

(iii) Our customer service and business development departments may contact users and other participants in order to ensure your satisfaction with FiversWorld.com® and/or to ask how we can improve.

**(4.) Updating and Deleting PII**  
If at any time you would like to update your PII, please log into your account and access your Edit Profile page. If at any time you would like your PII to be removed from our database or believe that FiversWorld.com® has not adhered to these privacy principles, please notify us by email. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete your information and/or promptly detect and remedy any problems.

**(5.)   Links to Third-Party Sites**  
To the extent that links to other Web sites are contained in Posts on the FiversWorld.com® site, please note that they are not operated or controlled by FiversWorld.com® and FiversWorld.com® is not responsible for the privacy practices, security, or content of these third-party sites.

**(6.) Security**  
FiversWorld.com® uses multiple security procedures and practices to protect from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification and disclosure the PII requested from users. All PII is password protected through PayPal. All passwords use 160 bit encryption. PayPal® uses 128-bit secure socket layer (SSL) technology and digital certificates to encrypt and authenticate transactions (credit card and other payments). SSL creates a secured connection between our web servers and your browser, which protects against unauthorized access to transmitted data and supports data being sent only to intended recipients. Our database logs important changes so that unauthorized transactions can be quickly reversed.

(i) Our main servers are locked and hosted by a leading provider of Internet access to enterprises with mission-critical Internet application requirements. Access to the host environment is highly secure. Biometric scanning, 24/7 onsite staff monitoring, and other safeguards are utilized. In addition, back-up servers that are stripped of email addresses, passwords, and credit card information are located in an office that is locked outside of normal business hours.

(ii) Despite these security procedures and practices, as is the case with all computer networks connected to the Internet, FiversWorld.com® cannot guarantee the security of your PII or any other information provided over the Internet and will not be responsible for breaches of security.

**(7.) Updates to This Policy**  
By visiting FiversWorld.com, you are accepting this policy as it may be amended from time to time. Please check the date of this Policy each time you visit to ensure that you are aware of the most current version. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, please do not use this site.

FiversWorld.com® reserves the right to update this policy at any time without prior notice. Material updates will take effect 30 days after initial posting on this site.

**(8.) Contact Us**  
If you have questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by [clicking here](https://fiversworld.zendesk.com/)
